woof
呜
playing tricks at the playground
在操场玩游戏游戏
who's there what's going on I'm stuck to
我被困在
the slide
我被胶片卡在幻灯片上
something's wrong
有点不对劲
picture
图片图片图片
oh
图片哦
what's wrong
什么是错的
it's right there
碞ê
a monster let me have a look
就在那里,一个怪物 让我看看
一个怪物 让我看看
a monster let me have a look
there's nothing here
这里什么都没有
oh it's not moving
哦,它不动了
what's going on
哦,它不动 是什么正在发生
let's go
我们走
watch out
当心
a little elephant are you all right I'm
一只小象,你没事吧,我没事
fine
小大象,你没事吧 我很好,我没事
Sheriff Labrador little elephants and I
拉布拉多警长 小象和我
were playing on the Seesaw and I don't
拉布拉多警长小象 我和我在Seesaw上玩
我当时在赛锯上玩,我不玩
were playing on the Seesaw and I don't
know why but he suddenly flew away
我不知道为什么,他突然飞走了
handprints someone must have been here
一定有人来过这里
did you see anyone no I
一定有人在这里 看见任何人没有我
but no one saw it hmm
但没人看到它,嗯
I think it must have been someone who's
我想一定是某个人
good at camouflaging
我想一定是一个很擅长照相的人
then how do we find the suspect
那么我们如何找到嫌疑人?
I have an idea
那我们怎么找到疑犯? 我有一个想法
foreign
外国
fish no
无鱼
no
无 无
that's it wonderful
不,这是美妙的
如此美妙
that's it wonderful
it's coming
多么美妙啊 即将到来
now
现在
Labradors
拉布拉多人体
look it's chameleon oh no they found me
看,是变色龙啊 不不,他们找到了我
oh God
哦,上帝啊
over there
那边
hurry
快点
he's engaged
他订婚了
we'll never play tricks on others again
我们再也不会对别人耍花招了
本字幕由AI大模型生成